[{"answer": "It was -- you know, it was very much how we've been around Elizabeth.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "How would you describe the occasion?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "She was lovely.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "What was she like as a godmother?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "She really did.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "I think better than most people, didn't she?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Yes, she did.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 51, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 50}, {"answer": "You know, it was a fairly short ceremony.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Describe to me since you're one of the very few people to be there, what was the atmosphere like through the day?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Oh, it's great.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "That's just amazing to watch, isn't it?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "You know, it's hard to say because I knew her as a person, and I don't know her as what's in the public eye.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What do you think is probably the biggest misconception about Elizabeth Taylor from your experience of knowing her?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Oh, unique in every which way.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "And Jose, finally, if you could use one word to sum up Elizabeth Taylor, what word would you go for?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "My life is pretty damn good.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "Is your life as good as I imagine it to be?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "And if I do, I complain about some of the things I've got, I'd be being kind of a sissy about some things.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "You don't?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "With this movie.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "I am?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "That's strong.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Yes, that's cool.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Cool, isn't it?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "He'd love that, man.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "ORGAN: Yes, what would he think of it?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Just enough that my kids aren't going to have to worry about themselves, but enough that they're going to have to work for it.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How much?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Yes, you know that egg -- I have the number that I'm going, OK, I'm going to be fine, my lady is going to be fine, my kids are going to be fine.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 267, "question": "A nice egg?", "qSentId": 266}, {"answer": "Don't have to worry about them, but we're pretty thrifty.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "But do you still have to worry about bills?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Well, I spent one summer with my brother shoveling mushroom compost.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "It was sheep dung.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What was it?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, if you're too high on your horse, as my mom would say, shoveling some sheep dung for 20 days in the middle of nowhere is probably a good thing for you.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "What did it give you, shoveling compost?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I don't think it was.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Was the dream there then?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Were you a fan of the movies?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I saw two films before I was 17.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "\"Orca\" and \"King Kong.\"", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What were they?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "He used to play for the Green Bay Packers in 1953.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Because your dad was a football player?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "There was a day -- and mind you, there were many days leading up to this, but I was becoming restless with the idea of heading towards law school, which is what I thought I was going to do.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "And it hadn't been a career path, when was the moment you suddenly thought, OK, maybe?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Oh, I was relieved.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Were you relieved at the reaction?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "He was artistic as well as sporty?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "No, not that much.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Does part of you think ever, I would have quite liked to have been a lawyer?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "She's got soccer practice tomorrow, right?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "All I said was she's pretty.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "Do you think you're the first client to ever threaten me and my family?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "They're not the first ones I go see when I leave to go out to the theater.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You don't?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "Do I ever?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "-- comedy?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "If it had to be one or the other?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "-- it's very pacey.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "You like that?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Jammy Git.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "One what?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "It's an English euphemism for very lucky man.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "-- England -- England, what does that mean?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I would agree with you.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "I mean you struck gold, didn't you?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "And they -- I mean they are very exotic people?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I mean there's a -- you know, I spoke of her grace earlier.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Is that what attracted you to her?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "I mean, that's a great --", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "What was going on there?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "-- to not want to get married?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Are you against marriage?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Do you think you will get married?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Fatherhood is a --", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "And how's fatherhood?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "-- as good as you thought and hoped it would be?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "It's like even now, you look back with affection, don't you?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 751, "question": "You first noticed he never had his shirt on, right?", "qSentId": 750}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 777, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 776}, {"answer": "Enough.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "What did Martina say?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "I like drums.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "You love these things, don't you?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "Well, Mishka, he's with my record level -- label, Just Keep Livin Records.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "Mishka?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "Work-wise, I mean, that would be -- that would be an honor.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 857, "question": "Is that something that you aspire to or is there something else that's more significant to you?", "qSentId": 856}, {"answer": "We do the soundtrack.", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 869, "question": "You play the bongos?", "qSentId": 868}, {"answer": "Jeez --", "docId": "110325pmt", "aSentId": 887, "question": "And even though you don't want to put yourself through any kind of epitaph, if I held you down and forced you to, what would you like on the Matthew McConaughey tombstone?", "qSentId": 886}]